<doc>
  <p>This demonstration system contains:</p>
    <li>Randomly generated data about people and repository items.</li>
    <li>The recommended Haplo RM Repository schema for a range of output types, (including datasets, collections, and practice-based research outputs) based on the Datacite and Dublin Core metadata standards.</li>
    <li>Standard features for item upload, deposit review, harvesting from external sources, embargoes, Open Access, REF and RIOXX monitoring, OAI-PMH integration, request-a-copy functionality for publications under embargo, and requests for access to restricted items.</li>
    <li>Reporting dashboards for day to day overview and management of repository items and processes.</li>
    <li>A generically branded example public interface to the repository.</li>

  <h1>Impersonation</h1>
    <p>To see the system from the perspective of different roles and to try out each step of a workflow, you can impersonate other users.</p>

    <p>To view the system as another user:</p>
      <li>Click the name of the current user in the top right of the screen</li>
      <li>In the menu which appears, click <i>"Impersonate user"</i></li>
      <li>Choose a user from the list, or type to search.</li>
      <li>Click the <i>"Finish impersonation"</i> button at the top of the screen to return to the original user, or choose a icon in the top left to quickly switch between users you've previously impersonated.</li>

    <p>Impersonation is only available to IT Support users in a live Haplo RM Repository system.</p>

  <h1>Instructions</h1>
    <li>Impersonating a Repository Editor, click the <i>"Repository"</i> button on the right to see administrative menus.</li>
    <li>Use the <i>"Repository overview"</i> directory to find a research output.</li>
    <li>As an academic the <i>"My record"</i> button, second in the list on the right of the home page, links directly to pages about your use of the system.</li>
    <li>From your profile you can add research outputs to the system, through links on the right hand side of the "My record page". Research outputs only be included in the public interface to the repository once they have been approved by repository editors through the deposit review workflow.</li>
    <li>This deposit process can be started from the output record, once it has been saved.</li>
    <li>When a workflow is in progress, it'll show who it's currently with on the right hand side. Impersonate the user to try the next step in the workflow.</li>
    <li>To see the notification emails the system would send, click the user name in the top right, then <i>"Test email viewer"</i>. (only available for administrator users)</li>
    <li>Files which are under embargo, or with a restricted access level, can be requested by external users through the public interface to the repository.</li>

</doc>
